Hey, how's it going?
Good.
How are you?
Nice to meet you, Mehdi.
So your main claim is that Trump pardoned some people
from January 6th.
By the way, I was there.
I saw it all firsthand.
About a football field away, the smoke in my eyes, bloodied.
It was a crazy day.
Were you convicted of any crimes?
No, of course not, because I didn't enter the building.
You know, stayed very peaceful.
But your entire claim is that he pardons.
That's not my entire claim.
Your bet's basically, you keep bringing it up.
All you do is bring it up.
OK, I'll mention some other people.
Let me say this.
Are you OK with his pardoning of Paul Wolchak, who
stole money from his employees?
You keep talking about pardoning.
For nine former members of Congress.
That's my claim.
You keep talking about pardoning.
He keeps pardoning criminals.
That makes him pro-criminal.
You know who else pardoned a big criminal?
Go on.
Hunter Biden was pardoned by his father.
He did crack cocaine, and he had hookers there, too.
I'm with you all.
But then why don't you claim that Biden was pro-crime?
I think Joe Biden, in that instance, was pro-crime.
He shouldn't have done it.
Well, he was overall pro-crime, just because he did that.
No, but Joe Biden didn't just.
So if it was just a pardon, then you'd be fine.
But I already mentioned, there's also
the fact that Joe Biden wasn't actually
convicted criminal in office.
Trump has committed crimes.
Trump hangs around with criminals.
He spent much of the 80s hanging around with the New York mob.
He hung around with Jeffrey Epstein and Ghislaine Maxwell.
Well, that's sneaky.
I can keep going.
Jeffrey Epstein lived in West Palm Beach in the area,
and that's the closest golf course he could go to.
Do you think Donald Trump is in the Epstein files?
So he paid.
As soon as Trump found out that Epstein.
Do you think Donald Trump is in the Epstein files?
No, I do not.
And you're asking me to explain.
Let me explain.
Let me explain this.
He lived in the area in Mar-a-Lago, near Mar-a-Lago.
So he bought, obviously, a ticket to go in there.
As soon as Trump found out that Epstein
had done all those bad things, immediate ban from Mar-a-Lago.
That's not true, but OK.
Immediate ban from Mar-a-Lago.
Yes, it is.
That's not true.
Yes, it is, 100%.
In fact, Ghislaine Maxwell recruited some of the girls
of abuse from Mar-a-Lago.
So listen to this.
From Mar-a-Lago.
That's pretty outrageous, right?
Elon Musk tweeted that out in a fit of rage, OK?
Do you really think.
Sometimes people tell the truth when they're angry.
He literally said that Elon Musk had
no access to the Epstein files.
Kash Patel said that Epstein killed himself.
Do you agree with that?
Whatever he says goes, then.
Yeah, I don't care.
You do?
He knows more information than I do.
A lot of MAGA people are upset with Kash Patel for saying that.
But here's the actual claim.
Suddenly people are trying to vote you out
because you said you agree with Kash Patel on Epstein.
He knows more information than I do.
All right, pause.
That's time.
Please return to your seat.
Good to meet you.
Yeah.
Take care.
Surrounded is now a podcast.
Available wherever you listen.
Search Surrounded, plug in, and stay part of the conversation.
Anywhere, anytime.
My next claim is that Donald Trump
is defying the Constitution.